Jonathan Tan Pham

9189 E Oxford Dr., Denver, CO 80237 C: (720) 612 3386 · jonathan.pham@ucdenver.edu

linkedin.com/in/jonathan-pham • jonathanpham5.github.io

Summary

Highly Skilled software development professional bringing more than 2 years in software design, development and integration. Advanced knowledge of Python and C/C++. Detail-oriented IT Professional with extensive experience in telecommunications and customer service. Troubleshoots highly technical issues with ease and patience.

Skills

- Java/C/C++/Python/Racket Proficient
- SQL Database and RDF Proficient
- Skilled with PHP, HTML, CSS
- Excellent Communication and Written Skills

- Windows and Linux Proficient
- Excellent problem-solving abilities
- Excellent Attention to detail
- Fast Learner

Work History

IT Professional, 06/2017 to Current

University of Colorado Denver - Denver, CO

- Help Desk at University of Colorado Denver Office of Information Technology
- Provided Support for PGP/Symantec Encrypted devices
- Provided Support for all devices (PC, Mac, iPhone, Android, Tablets, etc)
- Provided Support for Canvas (University's LMS)
- Managed User Accounts through Active Directory and for Canvas
- Troubleshoot and Surveyed Network Connections
- Support Provided via Phone, Email and Help Desk Chat

Software Developer, 01/2016 to 10/2017

Shavano Systems – Centennial, CO

- Worked on Project: AGNES (Automatic Generation of Network Element Software)
- Modified/Maintained Code Generator built in Racket Programming Language
- Modified/Maintained Network Code built in C Programming Language
- Implemented Automated Tests to test Network Code

CU Online Helpdesk, 05/2015 – 06/2017

University of Colorado Denver – Denver, CO

Education

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science at University of Colorado Denver, May 2017

Minor: Mathematics

Orgs/Accomplishments - Honors, Tau Beta Pi, ACM